=Love Lurking=
=الحب الكامن=
=Episode 11=
=الحلقة 11=
(Nian,)
(لنا،)
(I found Song Qian joined Wei Group three years ago.)
(وجدت أن سونغ تشيان انضم إلى مجموعة وي منذ ثلاث سنوات.)
(He's never left here or visited Tai City.)
(لم يغادر هذا المكان أبدًا أو يزور مدينة تاي.)
(One month ago,)
(منذ شهر واحد)
(after getting engaged to Wei Qing,)
(بعد خطوبته على وي تشينغ)
(he took over Wei Group)
(استولى على مجموعة وي)
(as the new executive director.)
(كمدير تنفيذي جديد).
(It seems he climbed up through marriage.)
(يبدو أنه ارتقى من خلال الزواج.)
(Could it be)
(هل يمكن أن يكون)
(he's really not K?)
(إنه ليس ك حقًا؟)
Qian,
تشيان،
do you know that female doctor from today?
هل تعرف تلك الطبيبة من اليوم؟
How would I know her?
كيف سأعرفها؟
Could it be that you forgot her
هل يمكن أن تكون قد نسيتها؟
after losing your memory?
بعد فقدان الذاكرة؟
I'm worried
انا قلق
if she discovers your identity in Tai City,
إذا اكتشفت هويتك في مدينة تاي،
she might become a threat to you.
ربما تصبح تهديدًا لك.
We should eliminate her early.
ينبغي علينا القضاء عليها مبكرا.
She's just a doctor.
إنها مجرد طبيبة.
She can't threaten me.
لا يمكنها أن تهددني.
Then don't see her again.
ثم لا تراها مرة أخرى.
She seems like a troublemaker.
يبدو أنها مثيرة للمشاكل.
Okay.
تمام.
It's too late today.
لقد فات الأوان اليوم.
I'll have Zheng take you back.
سأطلب من تشنغ أن يأخذك مرة أخرى.
I'm not going back.
لن أعود.
I absolutely won't go back tonight.
لن أعود الليلة على الإطلاق.
I'm your fiancee.
انا خطيبتك
Yet you still haven't touched me.
ولكنك لم تلمسني بعد.
I was injured before.
لقد تعرضت للإصابة من قبل.
You know that.
أنت تعرف ذلك.
I haven't fully recovered.
لم أتعافى بشكل كامل.
I don't care.
لا أهتم.
I'm staying here tonight.
سأبقى هنا الليلة.
Be good.
كن جيدا.
Your brother and I have matters to handle.
أنا وأخوك لدينا أمور يجب التعامل معها.
Zheng,
تشنغ،
take Miss Wei home first.
خذ الآنسة وي إلى المنزل أولاً.
Yes.
نعم.
Gu Nian
قو نيان
got the dean's phone.
حصلت على هاتف العميد.
We must get rid of her immediately.
يجب علينا التخلص منها فورًا.
(Nian,)
(لنا،)
(I've unlocked the dean's phone gallery.)
(لقد قمت بفتح معرض هاتف العميد.)
(Wei Group?)
(مجموعة وي؟)
(These photos were important enough to encrypt.)
(كانت هذه الصور مهمة بما يكفي لتشفيرها.)
Could it be
هل يمكن أن يكون
the dean's death is related to the Wei Group?
هل موت العميد مرتبط بمجموعة وي؟
Dr. Gu, please wait here for a moment.
دكتور جو، من فضلك انتظر هنا لحظة.
Our representative will arrive shortly.
سوف يصل ممثلنا قريبا.
Okay, thank you.
حسنًا، شكرًا لك.
You're welcome.
على الرحب والسعة.
(What exactly is in the photos?)
(ما هو الموجود في الصور بالضبط؟)
(The background looks like Wei Group's warehouse.)
(الخلفية تبدو وكأنها مستودع مجموعة وي.)
(But how do I find it?)
(ولكن كيف أجده؟)
Dr. Gu.
الدكتور جو.
I didn't expect this.
لم أتوقع هذا.
Mr. Song?
السيد سونغ؟
We meet again.
نلتقي مرة أخرى.
You're the person in charge of the project?
هل أنت الشخص المسؤول عن المشروع؟
Is that surprising?
هل هذا مفاجئ؟
May our collaboration go well.
أتمنى أن يسير تعاوننا على ما يرام.
May it go well.
أتمنى أن يكون كل شيء على ما يرام.
Let's conclude this morning's discussion.
لنختتم مناقشة هذا الصباح.
Meeting adjourned.
تم رفع الاجتماع.
- Okay, Mr. Song. - Okay.
- حسنًا، سيد سونغ. - حسنًا.
Dr. Gu,
الدكتور جو،
have lunch together?
نتناول الغداء معًا؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I already have plans.
لدي خطط بالفعل.
It's getting late.
لقد أصبح الوقت متأخرًا.
I'll take my leave now.
سوف آخذ إجازتي الآن.
Am I that intimidating?
هل أنا مخيف إلى هذه الدرجة؟
Dr. Gu,
الدكتور جو،
just days ago you were clinging to me.
منذ أيام قليلة كنت متمسكًا بي.
Now you're avoiding me.
الآن أنت تتجنبني.
Mr. Song,
السيد سونغ،
I think you've misunderstood.
أعتقد أنك أساءت الفهم.
We're simply business partners.
نحن مجرد شركاء عمل.
No clinging ever occurred.
لم يحدث أي تشبث على الإطلاق.
Nian.
لنا.
Senior?
كبير؟
Dr. Gu, this gentleman is here to see you.
الدكتور جو، هذا الرجل هنا لرؤيتك.
What brings you here?
ما الذي أتى بك إلى هنا؟
I'm here to take you to lunch.
أنا هنا لأخذك لتناول الغداء.
Okay, I'm ready to go now.
حسنًا، أنا مستعد للذهاب الآن.
Mr. Song, we are leaving now.
السيد سونغ، نحن نغادر الآن.
Won't you introduce us?
هل يمكنك أن تقدمنا إلى بعضنا البعض؟
This is our hospital's psychiatrist,
هذا هو الطبيب النفسي في مستشفانا
Dr. Zhou.
الدكتور تشو.
This is Mr. Song from Wei Group.
هذا هو السيد سونغ من مجموعة وي.
Hello,
مرحبًا،
Mr. Song.
السيد سونغ.
Heading out for lunch?
هل تريد الخروج لتناول الغداء؟
Then we're leaving, Mr. Song.
ثم سنغادر، سيد سونغ.
Okay. Let's all have lunch together.
حسنًا، لنتناول الغداء معًا.
I need to consult with you about something, Dr. Zhou.
أريد أن استشارتك في أمر ما، دكتور تشو.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
What would you like?
ماذا تريد؟
- You decide.
- أنت تقرر.
Would you like to try our couple's set meal?
هل ترغب في تجربة وجبة زوجنا المحددة؟
We are three.
نحن ثلاثة.
Three people can still order it.
لا يزال بإمكان ثلاثة أشخاص أن يطلبوه.
I'll take one.
سوف آخذ واحدة.
Make it two.
اجعلها اثنين.
Alright, please wait.
حسنًا، يرجى الانتظار.
Where is Mr. Song?
أين السيد سونغ؟
He went out to eat with Dr. Gu.
لقد خرج لتناول الطعام مع الدكتور جو.
Dr. Gu?
الدكتور جو؟
Gu Nian?
قو نيان؟
Miss,
يفتقد،
I'll take my leave
سوف آخذ إجازتي
if there's nothing else.
إذا لم يكن هناك شيء آخر.
Song Qian, You dare lie to me!
سونغ تشيان، هل تجرؤ على الكذب علي!
Nian,
لنا،
have a shrimp. It's good for your health.
تناول الروبيان. إنه مفيد لصحتك.
You two seem very close.
يبدو أنكما قريبان جدًا.
Of course we're close.
بالطبع نحن قريبون.
Nian's mother entrusted her to me.
أم نيان أوكلتها إليّ.
I'll naturally take care of her for a lifetime.
سأعتني بها بشكل طبيعي مدى الحياة.
By the way, Mr. Song.
بالمناسبة، السيد سونغ.
Weren't you consulting me?
ألم تكن تستشيرني؟
I want to ask how to treat amnesia if I got it.
أريد أن أسأل كيف أعالج فقدان الذاكرة إذا كنت مصابًا به.
(Amnesia?)
(فقدان الذاكرة؟)
Then you'd need to get an examination at the hospital first.
ثم عليك إجراء فحص في المستشفى أولاً.
Then I'll offer a treatment plan.
ثم سأقدم خطة العلاج.
Thank you for your help.
شكرا لك على مساعدتك.
You're Nian's friend.
أنت صديق نيان.
You're welcome.
على الرحب والسعة.
Still, thank you.
مع ذلك، شكرا لك.
Eat more. It's good for your eyes.
تناول المزيد من الطعام، فهو مفيد لعينيك.
Mr. Song, you don't like mangoes?
السيد سونغ، هل لا تحب المانجو؟
I'm allergic to mangoes.
أنا مصاب بحساسية من المانجو.
You eat.
انت تأكل.
Nian,
لنا،
what's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
I'm leaving now.
سأغادر الآن.
I need to sort documents.
أحتاج إلى فرز المستندات.
Nian,
لنا،
I'll go with you.
سأذهب معك.
No need.
لا حاجة.
What a coincidence. I don't like mangoes either.
يا لها من مصادفة! أنا أيضًا لا أحب المانجو.
(Is it a coincidence?)
(هل هي مصادفة؟)
(He's also allergic to mangoes.)
(وهو يعاني أيضًا من حساسية تجاه المانجو.)
I want to ask how to treat amnesia if I got it.
أريد أن أسأل كيف أعالج فقدان الذاكرة إذا كنت مصابًا به.
(Does he have amnesia?)
(هل هو مصاب بفقدان الذاكرة؟)
(But there's no scar on his shoulder.)
(ولكن ليس هناك ندبة على كتفه.)
(And he's never been to Tai City.)
(ولم يذهب إلى مدينة تاي أبدًا.)
Which floor?
أي طابق؟
The warehouse.
المستودع.
Me too.
أنا أيضاً.
Let's go together.
دعنا نذهب معا.
(Warehouse?)
(مستودع؟)
Where are all the boxes from the photos?
أين كل الصناديق من الصور؟
Why did the power go out?
لماذا انقطعت الكهرباء؟
Who's there?
من هناك؟
♪What is secretly stirring♪
♪ما الذي يتحرك سرا♪
♪From your mouth, I find it hard to describe♪
♪من فمك، أجد صعوبة في وصفه♪
♪What praises can disappear in just a second♪
♪ما هي الثناءات التي يمكن أن تختفي في ثانية واحدة♪
♪Vanishing without a trace♪
♪الاختفاء دون أثر♪
♪Waving hands to break free from the splendid cage♪
♪تلويح الأيدي للتحرر من القفص الرائع♪
♪Words against the heart, a pain slashes through the sky♪
♪كلمات ضد القلب، ألم يشق السماء♪
♪Floating into the endless night sky, the wind fierce and strong♪
♪تطفو في سماء الليل اللامتناهية، والرياح شرسة وقوية♪
♪Who is reckless, continuing to lose control, with impunity♪
♪من هو المتهور، الذي يستمر في فقدان السيطرة، مع الإفلات من العقاب♪
♪Let me disappear into the darkness♪
♪دعني أختفي في الظلام♪
♪Cannot see who is pulling the strings behind♪
♪لا أستطيع أن أرى من يسحب الخيوط من الخلف♪
♪The wound still aches, and the memory is not yet over♪
♪الجرح لا يزال يؤلمني، والذكرى لم تنته بعد♪
♪There are two endings, whether you understand or not♪
♪هناك نهايتان، سواء فهمت أم لا♪
♪Let me disappear into the darkness♪
♪دعني أختفي في الظلام♪
♪Cannot see who is tracking from behind♪
♪لا أستطيع رؤية من يتتبعني من الخلف♪
♪The heart still beats, total blood-red before my eyes♪
♪لا يزال القلب ينبض، أحمر اللون كالدم أمام عيني♪
♪Only one ending remains, whether it helps or not♪
♪تبقى نهاية واحدة فقط، سواء كانت مفيدة أم لا♪
♪Let me disappear into the darkness♪
♪دعني أختفي في الظلام♪